A Guide to the Rockefeller University collection of The Medical Letter publication FA241
Rockefeller Archive Center
- "Poison and Poisoning - The Initial Management of Acute Poisoning" (Reprints) 13:35, Issue 321, April 30, 1971 ("Gastric Lavage in Acute Poisoning - A Correction" 13:52, Issue 324, June 11, 1971), 1971 April 30 1971 June 11; 5 of 5 (Box 221, Folder 4)
- "Vitamin C - Vitamin C Were the Trials Well Controlled and are Large Doses Safe? " (Consultants: ML Drafts) 13:323, Issue 323, 1971 May 28; 1 of 5 (Box 221, Folder 5)
- "Vitamin C - Vitamin C Were the Trials Well Controlled and are Large Doses Safe? " (Pauling Correspondence) 13:323, Issue 323, 1971 May 28; 2 of 5 (Box 221, Folder 6)
- "Vitamin C - Vitamin C Were the Trials Well Controlled and are Large Doses Safe? " (Book) 13:323, Issue 323, 1971 May 28; 3 of 5 (Box 221, Folder 7)
- "Vitamin C - Vitamin C Were the Trials Well Controlled and are Large Doses Safe? " (Reprints) 13:323, Issue 323, 1971 May 28; 4 of 5 (Box 221, Folder 8)
- "Vitamin C - Vitamin C Were the Trials Well Controlled and are Large Doses Safe? " (CU) 13:323, Issue 323, 1971 May 28; 5 of 5 (Box 221, Folder 9)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy - Topical Fluorouacil (5-FU) for Premalignant Keratoses" (Consultants: ML Drafts) 13:323, Issue 323, 1971 May 28; 1 of 5 (Box 222, Folder 1)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy - Topical Fluorouacil (5-FU) for Premalignant Keratoses" (Manufacturer's Replies) 13:323, Issue 323, 1971 May 28; 2 of 5 (Box 222, Folder 2)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy - Topical Fluorouacil (5-FU) for Premalignant Keratoses" (Original Manuscript 13:323, Issue 323, 1971 May 28; 3 of 5 (Box 222, Folder 3)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy - Topical Fluorouacil (5-FU) for Premalignant Keratoses" (Reprints) 13:323, Issue 323, 1971 May 28; 4 of 5 (Box 222, Folder 4)
- "Cancer Chemotherapy - Topical Fluorouacil (5-FU) for Premalignant Keratoses" (Advertising) 13:323, Issue 323, 1971 May 28; 5 of 5 (Box 222, Folder 5)
- "Penicillins, New (Hetacillin) Hetacillin" (Consultants: ML Drafts) 13:49, Issue 324, 1971 June 11; 1 of 5 (Box 222, Folder 6)
- "Penicillins, New (Hetacillin) Hetacillin" (Manufacturer's Replies) 13:49, Issue 324, 1971 June 11; 2 of 5 (Box 222, Folder 7)
- "Penicillins, New (Hetacillin) Hetacillin" (Original Manuscript) 13:49, Issue 324, 1971 June 11; 3 of 5 (Box 222, Folder 8)
- "Penicillins, New (Hetacillin) Hetacillin" (Reprints) 13:49, Issue 324, 1971 June 11; 4 of 5 (Box 222, Folder 9)
- "Penicillins, New (Hetacillin) Hetacillin" (Advertising) 13:49, Issue 324, 1971 June 11; 5 of 5 (Box 222, Folder 10)
- "Diphenylhydantoin - Diphenylhydantoin" (Consultants: ML Drafts) 13:50, Issue 324, 1971 June 11; 1 of 3 (Box 222, Folder 11)
- "Diphenylhydantoin - Diphenylhydantoin" (Original Manuscript) 13:50, Issue 324, 1971 June 11; 2 of 3 (Box 222, Folder 12)
- "Diphenylhydantoin - Diphenylhydantoin" (Reprints) 13:50, Issue 324, 1971 June 11; 3 of 3 (Box 222, Folder 13)
- "Iodochlorhydroxyquin - Entero-vioform & Organic Neurologic Disease" (Consultants: ML Drafts) 13:51, Issue 324, 1971 June 11; 1 of 3 (Box 223, Folder 1)
- "Iodochlorhydroxyquin - Entero-vioform & Organic Neurologic Disease" (Original Manuscript) 13:51, Issue 324, 1971 June 11; 2 of 3 (Box 223, Folder 2)
- "Iodochlorhydroxyquin - Entero-vioform & Organic Neurologic Disease" (Reprints) 13:51, Issue 324, 1971 June 11; 3 of 3 (Box 223, Folder 3)
- "Heat and Cold Therapy - Hot water for Itching" 8:50, Issue 195, July 1, 1966 \ 11:60, Issue 274, July 11, 1969 \ 13:52, Issue 324, June 11, 1971, 1966 July 1-1969 July 11 1971 June 11; 1 of 1 (Box 223, Folder 4)
- "Antimicrobials, Side Effects - Principal Toxic, Allergic and Other Adverse Effects of Antimicrobial Drugs" (Consultants: ML Drafts) 13:53, Issue 325, 1971 June 25; 1 of 4 (Box 223, Folder 5)
- "Antimicrobials, Side Effects - Principal Toxic, Allergic and Other Adverse Effects of Antimicrobial Drugs" (Consultants: ML Drafts) 13:53, Issue 325, 1971 June 25; 2 of 4 (Box 223, Folder 6)
- "Antimicrobials, Side Effects - Principal Toxic, Allergic and Other Adverse Effects of Antimicrobial Drugs" (Original Manuscript) 13:53, Issue 325, 1971 June 25; 3 of 4 (Box 223, Folder 7)
- "Antimicrobials, Side Effects - Principal Toxic, Allergic and Other Adverse Effects of Antimicrobial Drugs" (Reprints) 13:53, Issue 325, 1971 June 25; 4 of 4 (Box 223, Folder 8)
- "Blood Coagulation - Treatment of Disseminated Intravascular Coagulation" (Consultants: ML Drafts) 13:57, Issue 326, 1971 July 9; 1 of 3 (Box 223, Folder 9)
- "Blood Coagulation - Treatment of Disseminated Intravascular Coagulation" (Original Manuscript) 13:57, Issue 326., 1971 July 9; 2 of 3 (Box 223, Folder 10)
- "Blood Coagulation - Treatment of Disseminated Intravascular Coagulation" (Reprints) 13:57, Issue 326, 1971 July 9; 3 of 3 (Box 223, Folder 11)
- "Diabetes, Therapy - Some Notes on Diet in the Management of Diabetics" (Consultants: ML Drafts) 13:58, Issue 326, 1971 July 9; 1 of 4 (Box 224, Folder 1)
- "Diabetes, Therapy - Some Notes on Diet in the Management of Diabetics" (Manufacturer's Replies) 13:58, Issue 326, 1971 July 9; 2 of 4 (Box 224, Folder 2)
- "Diabetes, Therapy - Some Notes on Diet in the Management of Diabetics" (Original Manuscript) 13:58, Issue 326, 1971 July 9; 3 of 4 (Box 224, Folder 3)
- "Diabetes, Therapy - Some Notes on Diet in the Management of Diabetics" (Reprints) 13:58, Issue 326, 1971 July 9; 4 of 4 (Box 224, Folder 4)
- "Obesity - The Treatment of Obesity" (Consultants: ML Drafts) 13:61, Issue 327, 1971 July 23; 1 of 5 (Box 224, Folder 5)
- "Obesity - The Treatment of Obesity" (Sources) 13:61, Issue 327, 1971 July 23; 2 of 5 (Box 224, Folder 6)
- "Obesity - The Treatment of Obesity" (Original Manuscript) 13:61, Issue 327, 1971 July 23; 3 of 5 (Box 224, Folder 7)
- "Obesity - The Treatment of Obesity" (Reprints) 13:61, Issue 327, 1971 July 23; 4 of 5 (Box 224, Folder 8)
- "Obesity - The Treatment of Obesity" (Advertising) 13:61, Issue 327, 1971 July 23; 5 of 5 (Box 224, Folder 9)
- "Nutrition & Diet Infants - Iron-Fortified Formulas for Infants" (Consultants: M.L. Drafts) [I] 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 225, Folder 1)
- "Nutrition & Diet Infants - Iron-Fortified Formulas for Infants" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) [II 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 225, Folder 2)
- "Nutrition & Diet Infants - Iron-Fortified Formulas for Infants" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 225, Folder 3)
- "Nutrition & Diet Infants - Iron-Fortified Formulas for Infants" (Original Manuscript) 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 225, Folder 4)
- "Nutrition & Diet Infants - Iron-Fortified Formulas for Infants" (Reprints) [I] 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 225, Folder 5)
- "Nutrition & Diet Infants - Iron-Fortified Formulas for Infants" Reprints [II] 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 225, Folder 6)
- "Nutrition & Diet Infants - Iron-Fortified Formulas for Infants" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 225, Folder 7)
- "Cyclophosphamide - Cyclophosphamide-an Immunosuppressive Drug" (Consultants: M.L. Drafts) [I] 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 225, Folder 8)
- "Cyclophosphamide - Cyclophosphamide-an Immunosuppressive Drug" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) [II] 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 225, Folder 9)
- "Cyclophosphamide - Cyclophosphamide-an Immunosuppressive Drug" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 226, Folder 1)
- "Cyclophosphamide - Cyclophosphamide-an Immunosuppressive Drug" (Original Manuscript) 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 226, Folder 2)
- "Cyclophosphamide - Cyclophosphamide-an Immunosuppressive Drug" (Reprints) 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 226, Folder 3)
- "Cyclophosphamide - Cyclophosphamide-an Immunosuppressive Drug" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:16, 1971 August 6 (Box 226, Folder 4)
- "Proctofoam - Proctofoam-Hc for Anorectal Disorders" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 5)
- "Proctofoam - Proctofoam-Hc for Anorectal Disorders" (Manufactures Replies) 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 6)
- "Proctofoam - Proctofoam-Hc for Anorectal Disorders" (Adverse Effects) 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 7)
- "Proctofoam - Proctofoam-Hc for Anorectal Disorders" (Original Manuscript) 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 8)
- "Proctofoam - Proctofoam-Hc for Anorectal Disorders" (Reprints) 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 9)
- "Proctofoam - Proctofoam-Hc for Anorectal Disorders" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 10)
- "Anticoagulants - Duration of Anticoagulant Therapy for Thromboembolism" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 11)
- "Anticoagulants - Duration of Anticoagulant Therapy for Thromboembolism" (Original Manuscript) 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 12)
- "Anticoagulants - Duration of Anticoagulant Therapy for Thromboembolism" (Reprints) [I] 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 13)
- "Anticoagulants - Duration of Anticoagulant Therapy for Thromboembolism" (Reprints) [II] 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 14)
- "Ulcers - Ulcerine and Treatment of Peptic Ulcer" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 15)
- "Ulcers - Ulcerine and Treatment of Peptic Ulcer" (Original Manuscript) 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 16)
- "Ulcers - Ulcerine and Treatment of Peptic Ulcer" (Reprints) 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 17)
- "Ulcers - Ulcerine and Treatment of Peptic Ulcer" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:17, 1971 August 20 (Box 226, Folder 18)
- "Tuberculosis, Chemotherapy - Rifampin and Other Drugs for Treatment of Tuberculosis" (Consultants: M.L. Drafts) [I] 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 227, Folder 1)
- "Tuberculosis, Chemotherapy - Rifampin and Other Drugs for Treatment of Tuberculosis" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) [II] 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 227, Folder 2)
- "Tuberculosis, Chemotherapy - Rifampin and Other Drugs for Treatment of Tuberculosis" (Original Manuscript) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 227, Folder 3)
- "Tuberculosis, Chemotherapy - Rifampin and Other Drugs for Treatment of Tuberculosis" (Manufactures Replies) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 227, Folder 4)
- "Tuberculosis, Chemotherapy - Rifampin and Other Drugs for Treatment of Tuberculosis" (Reprints) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 227, Folder 5)
- "Tuberculosis, Chemotherapy - Rifampin and Other Drugs for Treatment of Tuberculosis" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 227, Folder 6)
- "Acetaminophen - Acetaminophen, valadol an analgesic and renal injury" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 227, Folder 7)
- "Acetaminophen - Acetaminophen, valadol an analgesic and renal injury" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 227, Folder 8)
- "Acetaminophen - Acetaminophen, valadol an analgesic and renal injury" (Original Manuscript) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 227, Folder 9)
- "Acetaminophen - Acetaminophen, valadol an analgesic and renal injury" (Reprints) [I] 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 227, Folder 10)
- "Acetaminophen - Acetaminophen, valadol an analgesic and renal injury" (Reprints) [II] 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 227, Folder 11)
- "Acetaminophen - Acetaminophen, valadol an analgesic and renal injury" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 227, Folder 12)
- "Resuscitation - Manually Operated Emergency Ventilation Devices" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 228, Folder 1)
- "Resuscitation - Manually Operated Emergency Ventilation Devices" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 228, Folder 2)
- "Resuscitation - Manually Operated Emergency Ventilation Devices" (Reprints) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 228, Folder 3)
- "Resuscitation - Manually Operated Emergency Ventilation Devices" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:18, 1971 September 3 (Box 228, Folder 4)
- "Viral Infections - Antiviral Chemotherapy" (Consultants: M.L. Drafts) [I] 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 5)
- "Viral Infections - Antiviral Chemotherapy" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) [II] 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 6)
- "Viral Infections - Antiviral Chemotherapy" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 7)
- "Viral Infections - Antiviral Chemotherapy" (Original Manuscript) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 8)
- "Viral Infections - Antiviral Chemotherapy" (Reprints) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 9)
- "Medical Equipment and Devices - Dexon Polyglycolic Acid Suture" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 10)
- "Medical Equipment and Devices - Dexon Polyglycolic Acid Suture" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 11)
- "Medical Equipment and Devices - Dexon Polyglycolic Acid Suture" (Adverse Effects) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 12)
- "Medical Equipment and Devices - Dexon Polyglycolic Acid Suture" (Original Manuscript) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 13)
- "Medical Equipment and Devices - Dexon Polyglycolic Acid Suture" (Reprints) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 14)
- "Medical Equipment and Devices - Dexon Polyglycolic Acid Suture" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 15)
- "Prostaglandins - Prostaglandins" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 228, Folder 16)
- "Prostaglandins - Prostaglandins" (Adverse Effects) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 229, Folder 1)
- "Prostaglandins - Prostaglandins" (Original Manuscript) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 229, Folder 2)
- "Prostaglandins - Prostaglandins" (Reprints) 13:19, 1971 September 17 (Box 229, Folder 3)
- "Electrosleep - Electrosleep & Cerebral Electrotherapy" 13:20, [I], 1971 October 1 (Box 229, Folder 4)
- "Electrosleep - Electrosleep & Cerebral Electrotherapy" 13:20, [II], 1971 October 1 (Box 229, Folder 5)
- "Electrosleep - Electrosleep & Cerebral Electrotherapy" 13:20, [III], 1971 October 1 (Box 229, Folder 6)
- "Laboratory Tests - Drugs and Other Factors Affecting Laboratory Tests" (Consultants: M.L. Drafts) [I] 13:20, 1971 October 1 (Box 229, Folder 7)
- "Laboratory Tests - Drugs and Other Factors Affecting Laboratory Tests" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) [II] 13:20, 1971 October 1 (Box 229, Folder 8)
- "Laboratory Tests - Drugs and Other Factors Affecting Laboratory Tests" (Adverse Effects) 13:20, 1971 October 1 (Box 229, Folder 9)
- "Laboratory Tests - Drugs and Other Factors Affecting Laboratory Tests" (Original Manuscript) 13:20, 1971 October 1 (Box 229, Folder 10)
- "Laboratory Tests - Drugs and Other Factors Affecting Laboratory Tests" (Reprints) 13:20, 1971 October 1 (Box 229, Folder 11)
- "Gonococcal Infections - Treatment and Prevention of Syphilis and Gonorrhea" (Consultants: M.L. Drafts) [I] 13:21, 1971 October 15 (Box 230, Folder 1)
- "Gonococcal Infections - Treatment and Prevention of Syphilis and Gonorrhea" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) [II] 13:21, 1971 October 15 (Box 230, Folder 2)
- "Gonococcal Infections - Treatment and Prevention of Syphilis and Gonorrhea" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) [III] 13:21, 1971 October 15 (Box 230, Folder 3)
- "Gonococcal Infections - Treatment and Prevention of Syphilis and Gonorrhea" (Reprints) [I] 13:21, 1971 October 15 (Box 230, Folder 4)
- "Gonococcal Infections - Treatment and Prevention of Syphilis and Gonorrhea" (Reprints) [II] 13:21, 1971 October 15 (Box 230, Folder 5)
- "Gonococcal Infections - Treatment and Prevention of Syphilis and Gonorrhea" (Advertising: Package Insert) 13:21, 1971 October 15 (Box 230, Folder 6)
- "Gonococcal Infections - Treatment and Prevention of Syphilis and Gonorrhea" [Physicians International Symposium] 13:21, 1971 October 15 (Box 230, Folder 7)
- "Gonococcal Infections - The Condom as a Venereal Disease Preventive" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:21, 1971 December 24 (Box 230, Folder 8)
- "Probenecid - Use of Probenecid in Antimicrobial Therapy" (Consultants: M.L. Drafts) [I] 13:21, 1971 October 15 (Box 231, Folder 1)
- "Probenecid - Use of Probenecid in Antimicrobial Therapy" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts [II] 13:21, 1971 October 15 (Box 231, Folder 2)
- "Probenecid - Use of Probenecid in Antimicrobial Therapy" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:21, 1971 October 15 (Box 231, Folder 3)
- "Probenecid - Use of Probenecid in Antimicrobial Therapy" (Original Manuscript) 13:21, 1971 October 15 (Box 231, Folder 4)
- "Probenecid - Use of Probenecid in Antimicrobial Therapy" (Reprints) 13:21, 1971 October 15 (Box 231, Folder 5)
- "Antimicrobials, Sensitivity - Interpretation of Antimicrobial Susceptibility Tests" (Consultants: M.L. Drafts) [I] 13:22, 1971 October 29 (Box 231, Folder 6)
- "Antimicrobials, Sensitivity - Interpretation of Antimicrobial Susceptibility Tests" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) [II] 13:22, 1971 October 29 (Box 231, Folder 7)
- "Antimicrobials, Sensitivity - Interpretation of Antimicrobial Susceptibility Tests" (Original Prints) 13:22, 1971 October 29 (Box 231, Folder 8)
- "Antimicrobials, Sensitivity - Interpretation of Antimicrobial Susceptibility Tests" (Reprints) 13:22, 1971 October 29 (Box 231, Folder 9)
- "Antimicrobials, Sensitivity - Interpretation of Antimicrobial Susceptibility Tests" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:22, 1971 October 29 (Box 231, Folder 10)
- "Diagnostic Tests (Glucose) - Reflectance Meter/Dextrostix System for Blood Glucose" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:22, 1971 October 29 (Box 231, Folder 11)
- "Diagnostic Tests (Glucose) - Reflectance Meter/Dextrostix System for Blood Glucose" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:22, 1971 October 29 (Box 231, Folder 12)
- "Diagnostic Tests (Glucose) - Reflectance Meter/Dextrostix System for Blood Glucose" (Original Manuscript) 13:22, 1971 October 29 (Box 231, Folder 13)
- "Diagnostic Tests (Glucose) - Reflectance Meter/Dextrostix System for Blood Glucose" (Reprints) 13:22, 1971 October 29 (Box 231, Folder 14)
- "Diagnostic Tests (Glucose) - Reflectance Meter/Dextrostix System for Blood Glucose" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:22, 1971 October 29 (Box 231, Folder 15)
- "Air Pollution - Cigarette Smoking and Carbon Monoxide" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:22, 1971 November 12 (Box 232, Folder 1)
- "Air Pollution - Cigarette Smoking and Carbon Monoxide" (Original Manuscript) 13:91, 1971 November 22 (Box 232, Folder 2)
- "Air Pollution - Cigarette Smoking and Carbon Monoxide" (Reprints) 13:22, 1971 November 12 (Box 232, Folder 3)
- "Transplantation - Transplantation of Organs Other Than Kidneys" (Consultants: M.L. Drafts) [I] 13:23, 1971 November 12 (Box 232, Folder 4)
- "Transplantation - Transplantation of Organs Other Than Kidneys" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) [II] 13:23, 1971 November 12 (Box 232, Folder 5)
- "Transplantation - Transplantation of Organs Other Than Kidneys" (Original Manuscript) 13:23, 1971 November 12 (Box 232, Folder 6)
- "Transplantation - Transplantation of Organs Other Than Kidneys" (Reprints) [I] 13:23, 1971 November 12 (Box 232, Folder 7)
- "Transplantation - Transplantation of Organs Other Than Kidneys" (Reprints) [II] 13:23, 1971 November 12 (Box 232, Folder 8)
- "Antacid - Antacid Therapy for Peptic Ulcer" (Consultants: M.L. Drafts) [I] 13:23, 1971 November 12 (Box 232, Folder 9)
- "Antacid - Antacid Therapy for Peptic Ulcer" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) [II] 13:23, 1971 November 12 (Box 233, Folder 1)
- "Antacid - Antacid Therapy for Peptic Ulcer" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:23, 1971 November 12 (Box 233, Folder 2)
- "Antacid - Antacid Therapy for Peptic Ulcer" (Adverse Effects) 13:23, 1971 November 12 (Box 233, Folder 3)
- "Antacid - Antacid Therapy for Peptic Ulcer" (Reprints) 13:23, 1971 November 12 (Box 233, Folder 4)
- "Antacid - Antacid Therapy for Peptic Ulcer" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:23, 1971 November 12 (Box 233, Folder 5)
- "Vitamins, E - Vitamin E (Consultants: M.L. Drafts) [I] 13:24, 1971 November 26 (Box 233, Folder 6)
- "Vitamins, E - Vitamin E (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) [II] 13:24, 1971 November 26 (Box 233, Folder 7)
- "Vitamins, E - Vitamin E (Original Manuscript) 13:24, 1971 November 26 (Box 233, Folder 8)
- "Vitamins, E - Vitamin E (Reprints) 13:24, 1971 November 26 (Box 233, Folder 9)
- "Vitamins, E - Vitamin E (Reprints) 13:24, 1971 November 26 (Box 233, Folder 10)
- "Nitrofurantotin - Nitrofurantotin" (Consultants: M.L. Drafts) [I] 13:24, 1971 November 26 (Box 234, Folder 1)
- "Nitrofurantotin - Nitrofurantotin" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) [II] 13:24, 1971 November 26 (Box 234, Folder 2)
- "Nitrofurantotin - Nitrofurantotin" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:24, 1971 November 26 (Box 234, Folder 3)
- "Nitrofurantotin - Nitrofurantotin" (Adverse Effects) 13:24, 1971 November 26 (Box 234, Folder 4)
- "Nitrofurantotin - Nitrofurantotin" (Original Manuscript) 13:24-100, 1971 November 26 (Box 234, Folder 5)
- "Nitrofurantotin - Nitrofurantotin" (Reprints) 13:24, 1971 November 26 (Box 234, Folder 6)
- "Nitrofurantotin - Nitrofurantotin" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:24, 1971 November 26 (Box 234, Folder 7)
- "Diethylpropion - Diethylpropion, An Appetite Suppressant" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 234, Folder 8)
- "Diethylpropion - Diethylpropion, An Appetite Suppressant" (Manufacturers Replies) [I] 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 234, Folder 9)
- "Diethylpropion - Diethylpropion, An Appetite Suppressant" (Manufacturers Replies) [II] 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 234, Folder 10)
- "Diethylpropion - Diethylpropion, An Appetite Suppressant" (Adverse Effects) 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 234, Folder 11)
- "Diethylpropion - Diethylpropion, An Appetite Suppressant" (Reprints) [I] 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 234, Folder 12)
- "Diethylpropion - Diethylpropion, An Appetite Suppressant" (Reprints) [II] 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 235, Folder 1)
- "Diethylpropion - Diethylpropion, An Appetite Suppressant" (Reprints) [III] 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 235, Folder 2)
- "Diethylpropion - Diethylpropion, An Appetite Suppressant" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 235, Folder 3)
- "Antihistamines - Choice of Antihistamines" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 235, Folder 4)
- "Antihistamines - Choice of Antihistamines" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 235, Folder 5)
- "Antihistamines - Choice of Antihistamines" (Original Manuscript) 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 235, Folder 6)
- "Antihistamines - Choice of Antihistamines" (Reprints) 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 235, Folder 7)
- "Antihistamines - Choice of Antihistamines" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:25, 1971 December 10 (Box 235, Folder 8)
- "Spectinomycin - Spectinomycin, A New Antibiotic For Genital Gonorrhea" (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:26, 1971 December (Box 235, Folder 9)
- "Spectinomycin - Spectinomycin, A New Antibiotic For Genital Gonorrhea" (Manufacturers Replies) 13:26, 1971 December (Box 235, Folder 10)
- "Spectinomycin - Spectinomycin, A New Antibiotic For Genital Gonorrhea" (Original Manuscript) 13:26, 1971 December (Box 235, Folder 11)
- "Spectinomycin - Spectinomycin, A New Antibiotic For Genital Gonorrhea" (Reprints) 13:105, 1971 December (Box 235, Folder 12)
- "Spectinomycin - Spectinomycin, A New Antibiotic For Genital Gonorrhea" (Advertising: Package Inserts) 13:105, 1971 December (Box 235, Folder 13)
- "Corticosteroids (Meprednisone) - Meprednisone (Betapar) " (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:106, 1971 December 24 (Box 236, Folder 1)
- "Corticosteroids (Meprednisone) - Meprednisone (Betapar) " (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:106, 1971 December 24 (Box 236, Folder 2)
- "Corticosteroids (Meprednisone) - Meprednisone (Betapar) " (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:106, 1971 December 24 (Box 236, Folder 3)
- "Corticosteroids (Meprednisone) - Meprednisone (Betapar) " (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:106, 1971 December 24 (Box 236, Folder 4)
- "Corticosteroids (Meprednisone) - Meprednisone (Betapar) " (Consultants: M. L. Drafts) 13:106, 1971 December 24 (Box 236, Folder 5)